gogousenet.com 2010-05-27

# GOGOUSENET.COM

|  |   
---  
  
GoGoUsenet.com Privacy Statement  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

This privacy statement covers the site www.GoGoUsenet.com and all other sites in the gogousenet.com domain name space, such as help.gogousenet.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our user's privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices.

What personally identifiable information GoGoUsenet.com collects.

What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.

What organization collects the information.

How GoGoUsenet.com uses the information.

With whom GoGoUsenet.com may share user information.

What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under GoGoUsenet.com control.

How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact GoGoUsenet.com through <http://gogousenet.com/support.htm>

|   
---|---|---  

---  
  
§4. Cookies  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site. the user will not be able to use registered user features such as viewing full media or performing searches. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the Profile"section.

Cookies contain information collected at signup time, including IP address, referrer, and username.

|   
---|---|---  

---  
  
§6. Communications from the Site  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

§6.1. Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a validation email containing a hyperlink which validates their email address in order to complete registration on our site. Free members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Paid users do not receive these emails.

§6.2. Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account.

§6.3. Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email and our web-based contact form.

|   
---|---|---  

---  
  
§7. Sharing  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

§7.1. Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

§7.2. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

We do not share personal information with third parties with the following exceptions.

§7.3. Third Party Intermediaries

We use credit card processing companies to authenticate and bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

§7.4. Business Transitions

In the event GoGoUsenet.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

§7.5. Site Security and Abuse

In the event an attempt is made by any user to disrupt our service, circumvent our Terms of Service, or otherwise engage in activity which causes us concern regarding the normal operation of our service or site security, we reserve the right to share personal information with ISP administrators in order to resolve the issue and/or personally identify the user for further action

|   
---|---|---  

---  
  
§13. Security  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our user's information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our upgrade form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just surfing. In some cases, an upgrade form may not display the lock as the form is not displayed on a secure page. However, anything typed into that form will be submitted encrypted, and any re-display of the form with the information enclosed (for, example, data correction purposes) will be sent over SSL.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our user's information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. When new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our user's information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage in a locked facility. 

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can contact us via <http://gogousenet.com/support.html>

|   
---|---|---  

---  
  
§14. Correcting/Updating Personal Information  
  
|  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  | 

If a users personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct or update users personally identifiable information.

This can usually be done at: <https://gogousenet.com/pay_auth_edit.html>

Or by emailing our Customer Support at: <http://gogousenet.com/support.html>

|   
---|---|---
